The theme:
Movies that killed their franchises.
(Leonard:)Oh.
Like Jaws 4, Indiana Jones 4, Daredevil 1.
Miss Congeniality 2: Armed and Fabulous.
I mean, you know a movie's bad
when my homegirl Sandy B can't save it.
(Leonard:)Penny's working tonight. I'm in.
(Howard:)Not me. I'm having dinner with Bernadette
and her parents.
- Fun. We know how much you love that.
- It's torture.
(Howard:)Especially with her dad.
We have nothing in common.
(Sheldon:)You know what I like to do
when I'm forced to speak with those...
(Sheldon:)...beneath my intellectual station?
(Sheldon:)I bring up an interesting topic...
(Sheldon:)...like the difference between
Spider-Man and spiders.
(Howard:)Thanks, Sheldon.
I'll try that with my father-in-law.
(Sheldon:)No, you can't use that one. That's mine.
(Sheldon:)Try this one for an icebreaker.
(Sheldon:)Uh, despite popular lore...
(Sheldon:)...there is no place in the continental
United States, Alaska or Hawaii...
(Sheldon:)...from which one can dig straight through
the center of the Earth and come up in China.
(Howard:)Great. Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Actually, you can't have that one either.
It's too good. Sorry.
(Raj:)What about you, Sheldon?
Do you have plans?
(Sheldon:)Sadly, yes. Amy's taking me
to a memorial service.
(Sheldon:)It's for one of her colleagues
who is of Asian descent...
(Sheldon:)...so my planned conversational gambit
is to casually remark...
(Sheldon:)...that no matter how deep they dig his grave,
he'll never make his way back to China.
(Leonard:)That should lighten the mood.
What can I say, I put the "fun" in funeral.